Finding aid to the Classes of 1931-1940 records CA.MS.01015
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1931-1940 records
1927-2004
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1931.
CA.MS.01015
62.771 linear feet (139 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1931-1940 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Smith College -- Students.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College. Class of 1932.; Smith College. Class of 1933.; Smith College. Class of 1934.; Smith College. Class of 1935.; Smith College. Class of 1936.; Smith College. Class of 1937.; Smith College. Class of 1938.; Smith College. Class of 1939.; Smith College. Class of 1940.
- Class of 1931 records, 1927-1999; 5.917 linear feet (14 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1931 was the fifty-third graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1931 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1931, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - Addresses, 1929-1931 (Box 2028, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Music, 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1927-1928 (Box 2028, Folder 6)
  - Groups, 1927-1931 (Box 2028, Folder 7)
  - History, 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 8)
  - Ivy Day, 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, 1930 (Box 2028, Folder 11)
  - Junior Ushers, 1930 (Box 2028, Folder 12)
  - Last Chapel, 1931 (Box 2028, Folder 13)
  - Class Letters, 1946-1976 (Box 2028, Folder 14)
  - Class Officer's Handbook, 1991 (Box 2028, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1932 (Box 2028, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1936 (Box 2028, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 2028, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1946 (Box 2028, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1951 (Box 2028, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1956 (Box 2028, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1961 (Box 2028, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 2028, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 2028, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1976 (Box 2028, Folder 25)
  - Reunions-Recollections, 1981 (Box 2028, Folder 26)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 2028, Folder 27)
  - Reunions-Reunion Songs, undated (Box 2028, Folder 28)
  - Reunion Costume (Box 2028.3)
  - Class Secretary Card Files (Box 2028.2)
  - Class Secretary's Handbook, 1992-1999 (Box 2028.1, Folder 4)
  - Class secretary's Records-Change of Address Correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 2028.1, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Name/Address Change Lists, 1986-1989 (Box 2028.1, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Records-Name/Address Change Lists, 1989-1997 (Box 2028.1, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 6)
  - Senior Questionnaire, 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 7)
  - Songs, 1927-1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1929 (Box 2028.1, Folder 9)
  - Sophomore Push, 1929 (Box 2028.1, Folder 10)
  - Step Sings, 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 11)
  - Class Supper, 1931 (Box 2028.1, Folder 12)
  - Individuals A-L (Box 2029)
  - Individuals M-Z (Box 2030)
  - Davis, Mary Eleanor (class notes - Botany, Zoology) (Box 2031)
  - Davis, Mary Eleanor (post Grad) (Box 2032)
  - Davis, Mary Eleanor (correspondence, post grad, class notes) (Box 2033)
  - De Witt, Charlotte (memorabilia book) (Box 2033.1)
  - Paffard, Elizabeth (Biographical material) (Box 2035.1)
  - Paffard, Elizabeth (class notes, Landscape Architecture Botany, Zoology) (Box 2034)
  - Paffard, Elizabeth (class notes, Music, Zoology) (Box 2035)
  - Paffard, Elizabeth (Correspondence and trip to Europe) (Box 2035.2)
- Class of 1932 records, 1928-1997; 7.125 linear feet (17 containers)
  The Class of 1932 was the fifty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1932 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1932, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, financial information, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Addresses, 1928-1931 (Box 2036, Folder 1)
  - Class Baby, 1935-1957 (Box 2036, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1929-1932 (Box 2036, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1932 (Box 2036, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1928 (Box 2036, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1928-1929 (Box 2036, Folder 9)
  - Groups, 1928-1932 (Box 2036.1, Folder 10)
  - Class Granddaughters, undated (Box 2036.1, Folder 11)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1932 (Box 2036.1, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day, 1932 (Box 2036.1, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1932 (Box 2036.1, Folder 14)
  - Junior Prom, 1931 (Box 2036.1, Folder 15)
  - Junior Ushers, 1931 (Box 2036.1, Folder 16)
  - Last Chapel, 1932 (Box 2036.1, Folder 17)
  - Class Letters, 1934-1991 (Box 2036.1, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon, 1932 (Box 2036.1, Folder 19)
  - Class Meeting Minutes, 1928-1992 (Box 2036.1, Folder 20)
  - Officers, 1928-1952 (Box 2036.1, Folder 21)
  - Oversize Records (Box 2040.1)
  - Class Reunion Scrapbook, 1932-1952 (Box 2036.1, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1933 (Box 2037, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1937 (Box 2037, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 2037, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1947 (Box 2037, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 2037, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1957 (Box 2037, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 2037, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 2037, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 2037, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 2037, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 2037, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1977 (Box 2037, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 13)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, A-B, 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 14)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, C-E, 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 15)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, F-J, 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 16)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, K-L, 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 17)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, M-R, 1982 (Box 2037, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 1)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, S-T, 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, W-Z, 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 3)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies", 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies", 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 5)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies", 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 6)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies", 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 7)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, "Fancies", 1982 (Box 2038, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 10)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, A-B, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 11)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, C-D, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 12)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, E-G, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 13)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, H-K, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 14)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, L-P, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 15)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, R-S, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 16)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, T-Z, 1987 (Box 2038, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 2038, Folder 18)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, 1992 (Box 2038, Folder 19)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1992 (Box 2038, Folder 20)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1992 (Box 2038, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1997 (Box 2038, Folder 22)
  - Reunions-Memorabilia, undated (Box 2038, Folder 23)
  - Reunions-Reunion Songs, undated (Box 2038, Folder 24)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files (Box 2039.1)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files (Box 2039.2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1932 (Box 2039, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1932 (Box 2039, Folder 2)
  - Senior Questionnaire, 1932 (Box 2039, Folder 3)
  - Songs, 1928-1932; 1952; 1962 (Box 2039, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1930 (Box 2039, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore Push, 1930 (Box 2039, Folder 6)
  - Step Sings, 1932 (Box 2039, Folder 7)
  - Class Treasurer's Report Book, 1928-1972 (Box 2040, Folder 1)
  - Class Treasurer's Reports, 1981-1994 (Box 2040, Folder 2)
  - Individuals A-Hol (Box 2041)
  - Individuals Hon-Z (Box 2042)
  - Berliss, Ruth Ernestine (honors thesis, The Administration of the Public Employment Office in Great Britain, Canada, and Germany), 1932 (Box 2044.1)
  - Cobb, Elizabeth (honors thesis, Intellectual History of Northampton in the 1840s) (Box 2044.2)
  - Denniston, Ruth (class notebooks) (Box 2042.2)
  - Guernsey, Marjorie Louise (correspondence) (Box 2043)
  - Mahony, Mary Murray (correspondence) (Box 2044)
  - Wagner, Louise (Junior Year Abroad letters), 1930-1931 (Box 2042.1)
- Class of 1933 records, 1929-2003; 4.458 linear feet (16 containers)
  The Class of 1933 was the fifty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1933 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1933, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, notebooks, and other memorabilia.
  - Class Baby, 1955 (Box 2045, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 5)
  - Class Dean-Pierce, Helen, 1929-1933 (Box 2045, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1929 (Box 2045, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1929-1930 (Box 2045, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1929-1933 (Box 2045, Folder 9)
  - Class Historian's Notebook, 1930-1933 (Box 2045, Folder 10)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day, 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1932 (Box 2045, Folder 14)
  - Junior Ushers, 1932 (Box 2045, Folder 15)
  - Last Chapel, 1933 (Box 2045, Folder 16)
  - Class Letters, 1934-1975 (Box 2045, Folder 17)
  - Class Letters, 1976- (Box 2045, Folder 18)
  - Mascot, undated (Box 2045, Folder 19)
  - Class Officers, 1978-1983 (Box 2045, Folder 20)
  - Class President-Alumnae Council, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 1)
  - Class President-Class Committee, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 2)
  - Class President-President's Book, 1939-1973 (Box 2047, Folder 3)
  - Class President-Correspondence, A, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 4)
  - Class President-Correspondence, B, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 5)
  - Class President-Correspondence, C, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 6)
  - Class President-Correspondence, D, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 7)
  - Class President-Correspondence, E, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 8)
  - Class President-Correspondence, F, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 9)
  - Class President-Correspondence, G, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 10)
  - Class President-Correspondence, H, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 11)
  - Class President-Correspondence, J, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 12)
  - Class President-Correspondence, K, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 13)
  - Class President-Correspondence, L, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 14)
  - Class President-Correspondence, M, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 15)
  - Class President-Correspondence, O, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 16)
  - Class President-Correspondence, P, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 17)
  - Class President-Correspondence, R, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 18)
  - Class President-Correspondence, S, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 19)
  - Class President-Correspondence, T, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 20)
  - Class President-Correspondence, W, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 21)
  - Class President-Correspondence, X-Z, Officers, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 22)
  - Class President-Exhibits, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 23)
  - Class President-Fund, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 24)
  - Class President-Fund Chairperson, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 25)
  - Class President-Class Officer's Handbook, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 26)
  - Class President-Reunion, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 27)
  - Class President-Secretary, Jane Wilson-Kubler, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 28)
  - Class President-Treasurer, Elizabeth Reed Lyman, 1933-1938 (Box 2047, Folder 29)
  - Reunion, undated (Box 2048, Folder 3)
  - Reunions Class Meeting-Minutes, 1953-1988 (Box 2045, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1934 (Box 2045, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1938 (Box 2045, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1943 (Box 2045, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1948 (Box 2045, Folder 25)
  - Reunions-Questionnaire, 1948 (Box 2045, Folder 26)
  - Reunions, 1953 (Box 2045, Folder 27)
  - Reunions, 1958 (Box 2046, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 2046, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Correspondence, 1963 (Box 2046, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 2046, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1973 (Box 2046, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 2046, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1983 (Box 2046, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1988 (Box 2046, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1993 (Box 2046, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1998 (Box 2046, Folder 10)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1998-2003 (Box 2046, Folder 11)
  - Reunions-Reunion Chair Correspondence, 1935-1971 (Box 2046, Folder 12)
  - Reunions-Reunion Chair Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 2046, Folder 13)
  - Reunions-Reunion Chair Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2046, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 2046, Folder 15)
  - Reunion Chair Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 2048, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Chair Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2048, Folder 2)
  - Reunion Memorabilia (Box 2048.3)
  - Class Secretary, 1929-1933; 1973-83 (Box 2046, Folder 16)
  - Secretary's Minutes, undated (Box 2048, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Records A-M (Box 2047.1)
  - Class Secretary's Records N-Z (Box 2047.2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 17)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 18)
  - Senior Dramatics Photographs, 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 6)
  - Senior Questionnaire, 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 19)
  - Senior Questionnaire, 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 7)
  - Songs, 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 8)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2046, Folder 20)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1931 (Box 2048, Folder 9)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1931 (Box 2046, Folder 21)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1931 (Box 2046, Folder 22)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1931 (Box 2048, Folder 10)
  - Step Sings, 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 23)
  - Step Sings, 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 11)
  - Class Supper, 1933 (Box 2046, Folder 24)
  - Class Supper, 1933 (Box 2048, Folder 12)
  - Treasurer Expenses, 1930-1996 (Box 2048, Folder 13)
  - Treasurer Expenses, 1930-1996 (Box 2046, Folder 25)
  - Individuals A-C (Box 2048.1)
  - Individuals D-M (Box 2048.2)
  - Individuals N-Z (Box 2049)
  - Bragdon, Helen Cushman (course notes) (Box 2050)
  - Clark, Dorothy Gilman (Box 2050.1)
  - Dibble, Doris (diploma) (Box 2051.2)
  - Greene, Kate (memorabilia, class notes) (Box 2051)
  - Greene, Kate (class notebooks, photographs) (Box 2051.1)
  - Mcllveen, Marion (scrapbook) (Box 2051.3)
- Class of 1934 records, 1927-1994; 8.792 linear feet (17 containers)
  The Class of 1934 was the fifty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1934 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1934, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Alumnae Council Reports, 1940-1943; 1960-1972; 1975; 1990 (Box 2052, Folder 1)
  - Alumnae News, 1955-1970 (Box 2052, Folder 2)
  - Books Given by Class or Class Members, undated (Box 2052, Folder 3)
  - Book Memorials for Deceased Class Members, 1939-1959 (Box 2052, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Vespers, 1933 (Box 2052, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Music, 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1984 (Box 2052, Folder 10)
  - Deceased Class Members, 1960-1968 (Box 2052, Folder 11)
  - Delphic Festival, 1927 (Box 2055, Folder 5)
  - Financial, 1954-1974 (Box 2052, Folder 12)
  - Financial Documents, 1959-1979 (Box 2052, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1930 (Box 2052, Folder 14)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1930-1931 (Box 2052, Folder 15)
  - Fund Agent, 1957-1964 (Box 2052, Folder 16)
  - Groups, 1930-1934 (Box 2052, Folder 17)
  - Ivy Day, 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 18)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 19)
  - Junior Prom, 1933 (Box 2052, Folder 20)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1933 (Box 2052, Folder 21)
  - Junior Ushers, 1933 (Box 2052, Folder 22)
  - Junior Year Abroad Program, 1932-1933 (Box 2052, Folder 23)
  - Last Chapel, 1934 (Box 2052, Folder 24)
  - Class Letters, 1936-1949 (Box 2052, Folder 25)
  - Class Letters, 1950-1959 (Box 2052, Folder 26)
  - Class Letters, 1960-1969 (Box 2052, Folder 27)
  - Class Letters, 1970-1979 (Box 2052, Folder 28)
  - Class Letters, 1981-1989 (Box 2052, Folder 29)
  - Class Letters, 1990- (Box 2052, Folder 30)
  - Lost Class Members, 1957-1974 (Box 2052, Folder 31)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1939-1989 (Box 2052, Folder 32)
  - Class Officers, 1961; 1989 (Box 2052, Folder 33)
  - Class Officers' Correspondence, 1975-1980; 1992 (Box 2052, Folder 34)
  - Rally Day, 1932 (Box 2052, Folder 35)
  - Reunions-Class Reunion Handbook, undated (Box 2053, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1935 (Box 2053, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1939 (Box 2053, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1944 (Box 2053, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1949 (Box 2053, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 2053, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 2053, Folder 7)
  - Reunions-Correspondence/Preparations, 1959 (Box 2053, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Correspondence/Preparations, 1959 (Box 2053, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 2053, Folder 10)
  - Reunions-Correspondence/Preparations, 1964 (Box 2053, Folder 11)
  - Reunions-Correspondence/Preparations, 1964 (Box 2053, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 2053.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 2053.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Preparations, 1974 (Box 2053.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunions-Photo Album, 1974 (Box 2053.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-Special Gift, 1974 (Box 2053.1, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 2053.1, Folder 6)
  - Reunions-Preparations, 1979 (Box 2053.1, Folder 7)
  - Reunions-Post-reunion Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2053.1, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Scrapbook, 1979 (Box 2053.2, Folder 1)
  - Reunions-Scrapbook, 1979 (Box 2053.2, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1984 (Box 2053.2, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2053.2, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 2053.2, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 2053.2, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 2053.2, Folder 7)
  - Reunion Scrapbooks (Box 2055.1)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics-Music, 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, Individuals, 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, Groups, 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, Groups, 1934 (Box 2054, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics-Sikelianos Bibliography, 1934 (Box 2055, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics-Sikelianos Correspondence, 1934 (Box 2055, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics-Sikelianos Photographs, 1934 (Box 2055, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics-Sikelianos Publications and Clippings, 1927-1952 (Box 2055, Folder 4)
  - Songs, 1934 (Box 2053.2, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1932 (Box 2053.2, Folder 9)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1932 (Box 2053.2, Folder 10)
  - Step Sings, 1934 (Box 2053.2, Folder 11)
  - Class Supper, 1934 (Box 2053.2, Folder 12)
  - Works by A. Sikelianos: Athene Magazine (Box 2055, Folder 6)
  - Works by A. Sikelianos: The Death of Digenis (Box 2055, Folder 7)
  - Works by A. Sikelianos: Mater Dei (Box 2055, Folder 8)
  - Works by A. Sikelianos: Various Works (Box 2055, Folder 9)
  - Individuals A-Ma (Box 2056)
  - Individuals Mc-Z (Box 2057)
  - Densmore, Anne (scrapbook) (Box 2057.1)
  - Harris, Eve Lucile (correspondence) (Box 2058)
  - Harris, Eve Lucile (correspondence) (Box 2059)
  - Hoyt, Natalie (correspondence) (Box 2059.1)
  - Hoyt, Natalie (scrapbook, photo album) (Box 2059.2)
  - Lambert, Jeanette Evelyn (class notes, etc) (Box 2060)
  - Sampson, Norma (scrapbook and memorabilia) (Box 2061)
  - Sampson, Norma (scrapbook) (Box 2061.1)
- Class of 1935 Records, 1931-2003; 3.75 linear feet (8 containers)
  The Class of 1935 was the fifty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1935 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1935, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, undated (Box 2062, Folder 1)
  - Alumnae Association Ballot, 1960 (Box 2062, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1931 (Box 2062, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1931-1932 (Box 2062, Folder 9)
  - Groups, 1931-1935 (Box 2062, Folder 10)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1934 (Box 2062, Folder 14)
  - Junior Ushers, 1934 (Box 2062, Folder 15)
  - Last Chapel, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 16)
  - Class Letters, 1956-2003 (Box 2062, Folder 17)
  - Officers, 1955-1958 (Box 2062, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1935-1950 (Box 2062, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 2062, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 2062, Folder 21)
  - Reunions-25th Reunion Gift, 1960 (Box 2062, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 2062, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 2062, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 2062, Folder 25)
  - Reunions, 1990 (Box 2062, Folder 26)
  - Reunions, 1995 (Box 2062, Folder 27)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 28)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 29)
  - Songs, undated (Box 2062, Folder 30)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1933 (Box 2062, Folder 31)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1933 (Box 2062, Folder 32)
  - Step Sings, 1935 (Box 2062, Folder 33)
  - Individuals A-J (Box 2063)
  - Individuals K-P (Box 2064)
  - Individuals R-Z (Box 2065)
  - Anderson, Anna Ottilia (memorabilia book pages) (Box 2065.1)
  - Anderson, Anna Ottilia (memorabilia book pages) (Box 2065.2)
  - Bowker, Jane (scrapbooks, theater programs) (Box 2066)
  - Jones, Katharine Bruce (scrapbook from Junior Year Abroad in Spain), 1933-1934 (Box 2067)
- Class of 1936 Records, 1932-2000; 1.875 linear feet (5 containers)